freescore360.com 2019-05-25

# One Technologies

One Technologies – Privacy Policy
Last updated: March 27, 2019
OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY
We use the terms “you” and “your” to include any person who accesses the Sites, as defined in
the Term and Conditions, or purchases any product or service offered on the Sites (the
“Services”) for any amount of time. We use the terms “we”, “us” and “our” to refer to One
Technologies, LLC (the “Company”), which owns and/or operates this website, and our
employees, members, officers, directors, partners, affiliated entities, representatives, attorneys
and agents.
We understand how important your privacy is to you, so we are committed to assuring your
privacy. This page outlines all of the steps we take to protect your privacy, and what we do with
the information that you provide to us through our website.
What information do we collect?
In order to provide you with our services, we collect two types of information about our users:
Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.
Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of
who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this Site, such as registering for a
membership, ordering a product or service, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide
certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely
optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however,
we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing
address (including zip code), social security number, email address, employer, job title and
department, telephone, mobile telephone and facsimile numbers, assets, liabilities and other
personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the Site, you may be
asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the product or service, if you do not
provide the requested information, you may not be able to obtain the product or service you
want. You should be aware that if you enter any personal information during the information
request process and then click the “submit” or any other button on that page, the information you
have entered will be transmitted to us, even though you may not complete the process on
subsequent pages.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself
identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit
on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an
aggregated basis. This information may include the website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL")
that you just came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using and your Internet
Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the
World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission
Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks
like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the
destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your
v 4.0                                        Privacy Policy                             March 27, 2019

computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your
computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.
Protecting your information
We use SSL-encryption technology when transferring and receiving consumer data on our
websites to protect your personal information. We have partnered with Symantec or other equally
reliable encryption services to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we
have collected from you. The servers on which we store Personally Identifiable Information are
kept in a secure environment. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless
network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your
Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that there are security and privacy
limitations of the Internet that are beyond our control; the security, integrity and privacy of any
and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be
guaranteed; and any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a
third party. We make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent
unauthorized access to your private information.
How do we use information we collect?
We will use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site, fill orders,
improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve our product
and service offerings, and customize our site's content, layout and services. We may use
Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding
administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes,
troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Terms and Conditions
and this Privacy Policy. Your information may also be used by us or by third parties to whom we
transfer it to provide the products or services you have requested.
Some of our products may include alert emails that are sent on a daily, weekly or monthly basis.
These emails are part of your membership and cannot be disabled. In order to receive the most
up-to-date notifications and alerts, your email address must be accurate in your profile.
Some of our products may include text alert messages that are sent on a daily, weekly or
monthly basis. These texts are optional and you can change your settings at any time in your
portal. In order to receive the most up-to-date notifications and alerts, your mobile telephone
number must be accurate in your profile.
When you use our site, we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and
customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your
computer's hard drive (if your web browser permits) and can later be retrieved to identify you to
us. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us
to maintain a secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but
some parts of our site may not work properly in that case.
We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As
part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We and our third-party
ad server may collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP
address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code
associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular ad.
v 4.0                                        Privacy Policy                             March 27, 2019

With whom do we share your information?
We may sell, trade, rent or otherwise transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to others.
We provide the products and services offered on our website through contractual arrangements
with affiliates, service providers and other third parties. We and such third parties use your
Personally Identifiable Information to operate our sites and to deliver their products and services.
For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm
payment for products and services purchased on this site, release your Personally Identifiable
Information to the third party that will provide the products or services that you ordered, and
provide order information to third parties that help us provide customer service. We will
encourage our service providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your
Personally Identifiable Information by our service providers is governed by the privacy policies of
those service providers, and is not subject to our control.
We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic
patterns and related site information to third-party advertisers, but these statistics do not include
any Personally Identifiable Information.
Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally
Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally
Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena, or to cooperate with a law
enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those
who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement
agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
We also allow some of our employees and independent contractors access to both Personally
Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to enable them to assist us
with our business and provide the services and products that we offer to you. We endeavor to
have all such employees and contractors sign nondisclosure or confidentiality agreements with
us in order to protect your information.
From time to time, we make the email addresses of those who provide them to us available to
other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If
you supply us with your postal address online, you may receive mailings from other reputable
companies.
In the event that you unsubscribe from marketing email communications, we may share your
email address with our compliance vendor or approved marketing partners to prevent you from
receiving additional offers.
Privacy policies of third parties
When you sign up for services through our site, keep in mind that you may be interacting with a
third party that operates under its own privacy and security policies. Except as otherwise
discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses our use and disclosure of
information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site, and companies to whom
your information is transferred, have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and
disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the
policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our
site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use
v 4.0                                         Privacy Policy                           March 27, 2019

of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers
directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. You should
also be aware that unsubscribing from us will not automatically unsubscribe you from third
parties.
Updating your account information
Corrections or updates to your account information, including your email address, mailing
address and credit card information, can be made through the “Account Info” section of your
member account. If necessary, other corrections or updates to your information can be made by
contacting a Customer Care representative during our Customer Care hours.
Business transitions
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions,
customer information (both Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information)
may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that we, or substantially all of
our assets, are acquired, such customer information will be included within the transferred
assets.
Opting out
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional offers, you may "opt out" of
receiving these communications by opting out on our unsubscribe page or by clicking here to
unsubscribe. Our membership products may include alert emails or other informational emails
that are sent on a daily, weekly or monthly basis. These transactional emails are part of your
membership and cannot be disabled for persons who are members of these products.
Surveys and contests
From time to time, our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these
surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate
and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information
(such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code and age
level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey
information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of
our Site.
Changes to our policy
We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time,
so please review it frequently. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update
the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and
under what circumstances we disclose it. You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our
site Terms and Conditions, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its
terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.
You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to maintain a valid email address as a
registered user, review this site and this Policy periodically, and to be aware of any modifications.
Your use of the site after such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified
Policy, and your agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy.
Miscellaneous/contact information
v 4.0                                       Privacy Policy                            March 27, 2019

You must be at least 18 years old to use this site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose
Personally Identifiable Information about visitors who are under 18 years of age.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with
this site, please contact us at:
Attn: Compliance Dept
8144 Walnut Hill Lane, Suite 600
Dallas, TX 75231
The Customer Care team is available to answer your questions via phone seven days a
week.
Live representatives are available during the following hours:
Monday through Friday, 8AM to 8PM CST
Saturday, 8AM to 5PM CST
Sunday, Noon to 6PM CST
v 4.0                                      Privacy Policy                             March 27, 2019
